[Music]
[Música]
Okay, what's up family, what's up family,
bueno qué tal familia que tal familia
something really awesome just happened to me on Twitter, I'm
me acaba de pasar una cosa en twitter
going to give you a spin, okay, I
brutal os voy a pegar una vuelta vale
'm going to give you a spin,
voy a pegar una vuelta
how are you? By the way, today is stupid,
qué tal estáis por cierto hoy es boludo
Javi, watch the Turbo Plan video. My mother
javi ve el vídeo de turbo plan la madre
gave birth to him.
que lo parió
Javier, Argentine, doesn't exist. Well, the
javier argentino no existe bueno el
Turbo Plan video is precisely what I
vídeo de turbo plan precisamente de eso
'm going to talk to you about. These are the things that I'm going to talk to you about, okay, about the
voy a hablaros de esas cosas vale de lo
stupid thing and the Turbo Plan video,
de boludo y del vídeo de turbo plan
point number 1, the stupid thing, okay, it turns
punto número 1 lo de boludo vale resulta
out that I'll have insulted Xavi today,
ser que me haré ha insultado hoy a xavi
a follower or a follower in his
a un seguidor oa una seguidora en su
chat, by calling him stupid, okay, I
chat por llamarle boluda vale que yo
think stupid correct me if I'm
creo que boluda corregirme si me
wrong, it could be an insult or some kind of
equivoco puede ser un insulto o alguna
insult, well, not as such, but something like
bueno un insulto como tal sino algo como
derogatory, I don't know how in a
despectivo esto no se sabe como en plan
derogatory way, but I understand more like
despectivo pero entiendo más que es como
a wink, my weapon that passes, my weapon here
un guiño mi arma que pasa mi arma aquí
in Seville, no, or like a dude, not on the
en sevilla no o como un güey no en el
wave, no way, hey, me away, no, well, I'll have
wave no way oye me away no pues a mí
a follower of his who would have to
haré un seguidor suyo que tendría que
be from any region of the world where
será de cualquier región del mundo en el
this expression is used, he
que se utilice esta expresión le ha
called him today  stupid but I don't know I want to
puesto hoy de boluda pero no sé quiero
do how much and I will do it he answered him
hacer cuánto y me haré le ha contestado
with this delicacy, let's say a lot about
con esta delicadeza haber decir mucho de
what you think, it does
qué pensáis
n't kill you, they put on the stupid the referee
no te mata se ponen al boluda el árbitro
a [ __ ] where it says in the rule that
una [__] donde dice en la regla que
when you have me with others
cuando me se tiene con la de otros
separate them, let's
separarlos
go frank and a will your [ __ ]
haber franco y una voluntad tu [__]
mother is worth 2 I
madre vale 2
don't know, I don't know where the rules say
no sé no sé a dónde dicen las reglas
but I suppose somewhere it doesn't say I haven't
pero supongo que algún lugar no dice no
done such an stupid thing your [ __ ] mother or rather like
he hecho tan boluda tu [__] madre o sea
lately she doesn't cut herself off recently he called
últimamente no se corta hace poco llamó
the president of Madrid disgusting it's
asquerosa la presidenta de madrid es
true also recently we released a
verdad hace poco también que sacamos un
video an excerpt here he called
vídeo un extracto aquí llamó asquerosa a
the president of Madrid Ayuso disgusting he put up a
la presidenta de madrid ayuso se puso un
video site a video and he even calls an
vídeo sito un vídeo y llega a llamar
idiot don't be your [ __ ] mother that I did I have
boluda no sea tu [__] madre esa que he
n't seen anything like this since the chocas
hecho no veía algo así desde el chocas
and point number 2 what you're
y punto número 2 eso que me estáis
telling me about turbo plan I haven't seen the
comentando de turbo plan no he visto el
video is I haven't seen the video but it's just
vídeo es no he visto el vídeo pero es
now while I was putting on the music
que ahora mientras que ponía la música
look 9 minutes ago we're tweeting
mira hace 9 minutos vamos de tuiteos me
this happened to me there's a guy who
ha pasado esto hay un chico que me
writes to me he says hi javi turbo plan
escribe me dice hola javi el turbo plan
made a video talking  from dallas who
hizo un vídeo hablando de dallas que
sent a disgusting video the same day
envió un vídeo asqueroso el mismo da la
and the context of the video was that
y el contexto del vídeo hablaba de que
with the source code and the
con el código fuente y el vídeo
respective video was this one this kid
respectivo era éste está el chaval
sends me the [ __ ] video to me I ate
me manda el [__] vídeo a mí me he comido
the video or rather they send it to me I
el vídeo o sea me la mandan me lo he
ate a super disgusting video that
comido un vídeo súper desagradable que
tries to inform me more or less well
intenta informarme más o menos bueno
inform me I was talking to some
informarme lo estaba hablando con unos
friends about why the hell dallas
amigos que por qué [__] el dallas ha
did that of putting the source code a
hecho eso de poner el código fuente un
gore video that I think the video as
vídeo gore que creo que el vídeo como
such is not hosted on ohl but
tal no está alojado en estar de ohl pero
in the source code it says video
que en el código fuente pone vídeo dos
colon and it gives you the link and now it's a
puntos y te pone el link y ahora es un
gore video okay it turns out that people
vídeo gore vale resulta ser que la gente
are saying
está diciendo
the video that they published that sharing a
el vídeo que publicaron que compartir un
video about is illegal what a crime since
vídeo sobre es ilegal que delito ya que
the kid says it's a disgusting video in
el chaval dice es un vídeo asqueroso en
which dallas would be committing a
la cual dallas estaría cometiendo un
crime
delito
you're just like tintin face rolling with
eres igual que tintín cara revolviéndose
laughter face rolling with laughter
de la risa cara revolviéndose de la
confetti cannon face crying this is where
de confeti cara llorando de eso
we are facing the protagonist of the
estamos ante el protagonista de la
next pizza movie that has bought me
próxima peli de pizza que me ha comprado
or rather is buying everything ha  said I
o sea está comprando todo ha dicho
bought the king of salsa it is a
compro al rey del salsero es un vídeo
disgusting video in which Dallas would be
asqueroso en la cual dallas estaría
committing a crime and with all his
cometiendo un delito y con todos sus
balls he sends me the video he is saying
huevos me manda el vídeo está diciendo
that Dallas is committing a crime by
que dallas está cometiendo un delito
sharing that video okay and he is
compartiendo ese vídeo vale y me está
sending me the video with all his balls
mandando el vídeo con todos sus huevos
as far as I know let's see the disgusting video
que yo sepa a ver el vídeo asqueroso
Dallas is like my balls I have no
dallas está como mis [__] no tengo ni
[ __ ] idea why he put the video there
[__] idea porque ha puesto el vídeo ahí
I think the intention of putting the
yo creo que la intención de poner el
video
vídeo
video would be that when people enter
vídeo sería que cuando la gente entre en
the source code no and pressing
el código fuente no y presionando
trying to download the raulín this one not
intentando descargarse el raulín éste no
the free video then it is in collision with
el video gratis pues es en choque con
this gore video and they eat it or you are
este vídeo gore y se lo coman o tú estás
wanting to see the video without paying then they
querido ver el vídeo sin pagar pues te
eat it I don't think that is the
lo comen no creo que va por ahí la
intention not the troll hito of putting that
intención no el trole hito de poner ese
video but a video
vídeo pero un vídeo
sharing a video that I know is not
compartir un vídeo de que yo sepa no es
illegal it is not an intimate video I was
ilegal no es un vídeo íntimo lo estado
looking at it to see it is looking at it because it did not
mirando a ver lo está mirando porque no
fit me that I listened to a few
me cuadraba que escuchaba a unos cuantos
on youtube if it is not a crime it is a
de youtube si no es un delito es un
crime to put this video it is illegal not the
delito poner este vídeo es ilegal no el
video putting it is not illegal like it is
vídeo ponerlo no es ilegal en plan es
that you hit us with the [ __ ] video and
que nosotros nos das con el [__] vídeo y
especially for someone who can't
sobre todo para alguien que no lo
stand it, I just ate it, it's not that I like it
aguante yo me acabo de comer no es que
very much but well, I don't care at all
me haga muchas gracias pero bueno
but that it's
tampoco me da un poco igual pero que sea
a crime, it's not a crime, it's not a video
un delito no es un delito no es un vídeo
that he saw in anyone's privacy, which
que vio en la intimidad de nadie lo que
maybe it could not be very legal, but I
a lo mejor podría ser no muy lícito pero
understand that it's a bluff, it's what he's
entiendo que es un farol es eso que está
putting on twitter, I'm going to get
poniendo en twitter de os voy a sacar
the details from all of you who want a text
los datos a todos el que queréis texto
to report or I don't know what I'm there, yes, he
para denunciar o no sé que estoy ahí sí
sees it a little illegal at least
que lo ve un poco ilícito por lo menos
I don't know if that would be very logical, but what
no sé yo si sería muy lógico eso pero lo
is the video, not that I know of, putting
que es el vídeo no que yo sepa poner
videos, I mean, putting videos about, it's not
vídeos o sea poner vídeo sobres no sea
sharing, passing a video about someone
compartir pasarle un vídeo sobre alguien
if it doesn't violate anyone's privacy, it
si no vulnera la intimidad de nadie no
's not a crime, okay,
es delito vale
what a prince are you? I wondered if
tú qué príncipe eres yo me pregunte si
that could be illegal or something like that, it's weird,
eso podría ser ilegal o algo así es raro
no,
no
that is a crime, says the seals, let's see,
eso sí es delito dice el focas a ver
seals do not commit the crime of being exemplary
focas no ejerce el delito de ejemplar
because the basis of crimes that I don't understand
porque base de delitos que no entiendo
the reason for it being a crime, I don't understand and
el motivo de ser delito no lo entiendo y
the privacy of the deceased, his
la intimidad del fallecido
face cannot even be seen  no no no no I don't
no se le ve la cara siquiera no no no no
know it doesn't sound familiar to me it doesn't sound familiar to me it
sé no me suena no me suena no me suena
's a crime
que sea delito
that she's a [ __ ] like a
que ésta como una [__] así como una
Belgian but that she's a
belga pero que sea una
javi has a lot of haters on twitter I was
javi tiene muchos hater en twitter
amazed by the responses to your tweets
aluciné con las respuestas a tus tweets
wow wow
guau guau
now you realize what I have to
si ahora te das cuenta de lo que tengo
put up with how is it going to be a crime and the
que aguantar como va a ser delito y los
mangas and movies where it's also that it does
mangas y películas donde también es que
n't make sense to
no tiene sentido
share their affiliation if it's a crime in
compartir su filia si es delito en
some countries
algunos países
was talking about the gore video okay they
estaba hablando del vídeo gore vale que
put the link of a
hayan puesto ahí el link de un vídeo
gore video there if those crimes I
gore que si esos delitos
already said it does
ya digo sea
n't sound familiar to me nor is it a crime but
no me suena ni tampoco delito pero
trying to spread paid content like that
intentar difundir contenido de pago como
is clear I mean clear that is a
esos sí lo es claro o sea claro eso sí
crime however I mean however the one who
es delito sin embargo o sea sin embargo
downloaded the video that is that would
el que eché descargándose el vídeo eso
be a crime against
sí es eso sí sería delito contra la
intellectual property
propiedad intelectual
thank you very much I mean what they are
muchas gracias o sea lo que están
putting the dalai s you and I imagine it
poniendo al dalai s tú y yo me imagino
will be a bluff because he is not going to be so
que será farol porque no va a ser tan
stupid to put that tweet no like I
[__] de poner ese tweet no en plan
am downloading your data to
estoy descargando vuestros datos para
think that I don't think there is any virus I don't
pensar que no creo que haya ningún virus
know what a hick is talking to you no  I
no lo sé que os habla un cateto de no lo
know I don't think there's any virus that you
sé no creo que haya ningún virus que tú
give special elements of
le des especiales elementos de los datos
nobody's data is doing it to avoid
de nadie lo está haciendo para esquivar
the girls then they download the
a los niñas entonces se descargan el
link in the videos and summarize them but
link en los vídeos y los resumen pero
downloading a private
descargarse un video privado
shared video for payment and uploading it to other
compartido de pago y subirlo a otras
networks as many people are doing
redes como está haciendo mucha gente si
is a crime against
es delito contra la propiedad
intellectual property another thing would be that I would
intelectual otra cosa sería que yo
like is that for example comment on the
quisiera es que por ejemplo comentar el
video and put some excerpt
vídeo y pusiera algún extracto
normally here we respect
normalmente aquí nosotros respetamos
those paid contents whether we
esos contenidos de pago ya sea que lo
respect it but I believe that it is there
respetamos pero yo lo creo que está ahí
there the thing for example a
ahí la cosa por ejemplo yo una película
Walt Disney movie is also paid
de walt disney también es de pago
of this marvel movie a marvel movie
de esto de marvel una película de marvel
is paid and I have put here an
es de pago y yo he puesto aquí un
excerpt I understand that we
extracto yo entiendo que nos lo
respect it okay we respect it
respetemos vale nos lo respetemos
even Dallas says strike when you put
incluso dallas pone strike cuando pones
content that is for members but it
contenido que es para miembros pero
is taken with tweezers that of the seals
está cogido con pinzas eso de los sellos
if it is like that or not
si es así o no
but I think you will say I think he says it
pero creo que diréis creo que lo dice
for turbo plan no because he published
por turbo plan no porque publicó
content of the live and paid the
contenido de los live and de pago the
wind and it is that you touch the balls I have not
wind y es que tocas de los huevos no he
seen the turbo plan video but yes
visto el vídeo de turbo plan pero sí
turbo plan has said that it is a crime
turbo plan ha dicho que es delito
also the a turbo plan  in the video it
también los a turbo plan en el vídeo
says that it is a crime to
dice que es delito
post a gore video
lo de poner un vídeo gore
javier low series justified those that
javier serie baja justificada las que
on top of that scam people by posting that
encima que estafa a la gente puso ese
video
vídeo
alex I'm telling you that the video
álex te estoy diciendo que el vídeo no
is not a crime if you don't like it then look create
es delito si no te gusta pues mira crea
the penal code and change the law I'm not
tu el código penal y cambia la ley yo no
justifying Dallas for having
estoy justificando a dallas de que haya
promised that the video would last 40 minutes and
prometido que el vídeo duró 40 minutos y
that there are people paying for a 40
que haya gente pagando por un vídeo de
minute video and if the video lasts and the
40 minutos y si el vídeo duramente y el
shot keeps saying it lasts 40 on twitter it's that they
tiro siga diciendo dura 40 en twitter es
really are stupid any day
que de verdad hay k tonto cualquier día
the kids will stop doing it then they would
dejó de hacerlo la chavalería pues que
also teach there are
también enseñaría también hay que
some bans and get out take it by ass
algunos baneo y fuera tomar por culo
you know what true that could have helped
sabes qué verdad que pudo ayudar
people looking for the fifth leg of the cat
la gente buscando la quinta pata al gato
no but what an idiot you are an
no pero qué [__] que eres
idiot that I'm justifying I
[__] que estoy justificando te
'm telling you what there is it is not a crime
estoy diciendo lo que hay no es delito
[Music]
[Música]